== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Amy:)Here's your tea.
(Sheldon:)Oh!
(Sheldon:)Do not sneak up on a guy
when he's sitting on a log.
(Amy:)You know, if you really
want to be in nature,
(Amy:)why don't we rent a cabin?
(Sheldon:)Look, I'm sorry,
when did you even get here? I...
(Amy:)You know,
there's a cabin in Big Bear
(Penny:)that a doctor I work with
keeps offering me.
(Leonard:)Because he's
hitting on you?
(Sheldon:)She.
(Leonard:)Oh, good.
(Penny:)But I could get her.
(Amy:)We could all go
for the weekend.
(Amy:)It'll be fun.
Yeah... (clears throat)
Excuse me.
Here, look up "fun,"
get back to me.
(Leonard:)You and I could still go
and have a nice weekend.
(Penny:)Sure.
(Amy:)Come on, Sheldon,
let's go with them.
(Sheldon:)I hardly think so.
(Sheldon:)You be sure and say hello
(Sheldon:)to all the mosquitoes,
bees, bears, snakes,
(Sheldon:)possums, poison oak,